ed.
Here we go, Upgami, this time with Morning Musume。 23 and Sakura Oda of Morning Musume。 23's Sakura Oda.
This is a program that takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
We will be showing you our rehearsals, recordings, and other production processes.
Now then, let's start with a behind-the-scenes look at our two MCs.
I, FUKUMURA, performed at Japan Jam on April 30.
Project's 25th anniversary on the stage of Airi Suzuki.
Project's 25th anniversary. When I was invited to sing on stage with her, I practiced hard and worked really hard.
Yes, I was watching.
But after my stage was over, I was sweating.
And then the sweat cooled and my body stiffened.
All the way up to the time of the performance, I was moving my body to warm up my voice and vocalize.
And I thought my voice came out.
And I sang one chorus during the performance.
She said it was good.
And then the second chorus, we had to do a back-up dance, so I gave it my all.
Then I made the prescriptive mistake of coming back to the stage at the end of the interlude and not being able to sing because I ran out of energy.
That's very prescriptive.
That's right.
I gave 100% to that one song, and I wanted it to be more than 100%, and I was surprised at how much I couldn't reach the pitch.
It was very frustrating, but I am happy that I was able to give it my all.
I was also impressed by Airi Suzuki's perfect singing, dancing and facial expressions, no matter where she sang or danced or where she sang from.
I realized that I still have to work harder, so I started muscle training the next day.
That's great!
I, Sakura Oda, am so wonderful that the first outfit for the concert tour I'm doing now is a white long-skirted dress.
The first half of the concert tour we all wear white long-skirted dresses, but in the middle of the show, the skirts are designed to be taken off.
It's so long that you can step on it yourself, or someone else can step on it, or you can just stand on it and take it off, so I'm trying to come up with a new technique.
I'm currently going through a tour where I'm experimenting with nutrition and trial and error.
It's true that the tension is different from the usual tours, isn't it?
If you come to see the tour and see the members who are a little tense on their skirts, please think that they are doing their best and watch over them.
Please look at us warmly.
I'm glad you're watching us!
Now, let's start with this time's up-dated paper.
Beyonce Vocal Recording for "Yumeme to Dare Yume ga Naku Naku Yozora ni" (I can't even draw a dream in the night sky)
Please check out Shin Maeda's vocal recording of Beyonce's latest single, "Yume to Dare Yoru Sora no Yume wo Kakeranai Yozora ni" (I can't even draw a dream in the night sky).
Okay, then.
First of all, the entrance of the door tom is a little bit special, isn't it?
I'll try to get used to it a few times by listening to the clicks, etc. Please be aware of the entrance of the door tom.
I won't let you have a night sky where you can't even dream
I'll walk around humming your favorite melody
I won't let the night sky where I can't even sing of love
It's wonderful that you were born as you are
The phrase is quite long, isn't it?
So the point is the line above
I won't let you be the night sky
Yes, take a deep breath here, please.
Take a deep breath here.
That's right.
And then go in.
The rest is just you being you.
It's a short one, but just take it here.
If you don't last...
You were born to be...
You can smoke it anytime you want.
To have been born
It's very short, but it's okay to take a quick smoke here.
It's like that. You've just come in, right?
Please come in at the right time. One more for me.
I can't even dream. I won't let the night sky be a dream.
I'll walk while humming your favorite melody
I can't even sing of love I won't let you be the night sky
It's wonderful that you were born as you
That's too bad. Let me just take the second half of this one then.
Please let me film the second half.
I'll take it.
I won't let you be the night sky that I can't even dream of.
So many stars love you so much
Even when I can't draw anything, even when I can't feel anything
Don't forget that you were born on such a beautiful star
I love you
I love you so much that this place is light
Don't end with "I love you
I love you
Say it lightly.
Okay, then.
Enjoy another round of bright smiles.
I'm looking forward to it.
I won't let the night sky be a place where you can't even dream
So many stars love you
I can't draw anything, even when I can't believe itI can't draw anything, even when I can't believe it.
Don't forget that you were born on such a beautiful planet.
Thank you.
Thank you. Sorry. Take care. Bye-bye.
Bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye.
It's like I'm pushing those buttons.
Thank you, sorry, take care, bye-bye.
I'm going to say something like this.
Don't forget that you were born on a very beautiful planet.
Thank you, sorry, take care, bye-bye
I want to hold them all in my arms.
That's nice. I like your brightness.
I want to hold them all.
I want to embrace all of it, so that it doesn't connect here
I feel like singing again with "I want to hug you all." Please give me another one with this.
Don't forget that I was born on a beautiful star Thank you Sorry, take care Bye-bye
I want to embrace all of them
I'll take all of them.
It's another long phrase.
You and I are sharing the song, it's a miracle
I'll sing it again at the end, or rather, I'll remind you.
Miracle, it's a miracle we're sharing the song.
Miracle, it's a miracle, I'm going to cut it off, and then the la-la-la-la-la will come in.
I want to hold it all in my arms
I can't make it happen even in my dreams, the moment I'm here now
You and I are sharing a song, it's a miracle
Yes, that's what I mean. The cue is a little more out there, though.
Even in a dream
Please go in with a little more of an attack. Then let's go.
I want to hold them all in my arms
Even in a dream, it won't come true The moment I'm here now
You and I are sharing a song. It's a miracle.
Yes, it's perfect. Let's have it.
So that's all. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you very much.
That was cool. You were like a prince. I think this song has a different image depending on who sings it,
Beyonce has so many different singers with different voices, so there are so many different ways to express themselves, and I think it's a wonderful song.
I went to see the rehearsal for Beyonce's current tour. I went to see the rehearsal of Beyonce's current tour, and when I saw this song, I felt that I had been
I saw them play this song after the songs that they were used to playing, and I thought that the songs that everyone in Beyonc e had played before were good, but the new songs that Beyonc e had played before were not so good,
I thought again that the freshness and care of Beyoncé's new songs are also good, and I look forward to seeing how this song will change in the future.
That's all for now. This is Shin Maeda's vocal recording of "Beyonce: A Night Sky No One Can Paint Even a Dream.
The night sky that no one can defile is watching over us.
Beyonce's new single, Yume to Dake no Yoru Sora ni Now on sale
Are you alright? I'll manage!
Here's the next one! Angstrom's vocal recording I want to destroy it!
Here's a look at the vocal recording of Akari Takeuchi from Angulum's latest album Big Love!
Let's start with the A melody. Let's go from "Ain't You Quit Adventuring" to "I Want to Destroy It!
Yes, yes, yes. That pitch part is the same pitch all the way through.
Yes, yes.
I think it's better to separate the "I want to destroy myself" part from the "I want to destroy myself" part.
I said, "I want to destroy myself.
I want to destroy myself like that.
So, in terms of pitch and rhythm, there is no problem at all,
I want to destroy myself like that,
I want to push each note one by one.
If you become "have you stopped adventuring or are you becoming timid," you will become more and more timid,
Be careful not to become so.
Yes, let's go!
Pure.
Are you ever going to stop adventuring? Are you ever going to be timid?
Are you in a rut? Are you clinging to stability?
Are you making compromises? Are you stuck in the past?
When I find myself trying to be right...
I want to destroy myself like that.
Okay, let's go to the end of the song.
I'm not sure if that's true or not, but I'm just going with the tension.
I love it! I like it! I wonder if it's good!
It's good!
Well, you know, in the chorus, you say, "Let's do something new, let's change ourselves first, let's bury all the old ways of doing things.
Well, you say things like, "Change, you should change," and there are some negative words like, "Let's bury it, let's stop it," but, you know....
But, I think it's more like, "Let's change, we'll change too, so let's change together.
Let's do something new, something we have never done or seen before, something that will make us feel excited and young, that's the image I have.
Yes!
So, if I were to say just how exciting and thrilling it is, I would say it's like "Let's all go to Disney together.
I hope this chorus will have that kind of exciting and thrilling feeling.
Yes!
Okay, so let's go one more time.
I want to destroy the self that tries to be right when it finds itself in a situation like this.
Let's do something new. First of all, let's change ourselves.
No more of those old-fashioned equations.
Turn the other cheek and look for reasons why you can't do it.I'm turning every cheek and looking for reasons why I can't do it.
I'm done looking for reasons why we can't change.
I know who you really are, don't I? Come on!
Yes!
So, let's get to the main thing, shall we?
Let's go to the end.
I've been a coward.
I want to destroy it.
Oh yeah
I want to destroy it, I want to destroy it
That's what I'm talking about.
Yes, sir!
I want to tear down everything I've ever done I want to tear down everything I've ever been
Oh yeah!
I want to destroy it.
Yes, yes, that's what I mean.
Let's see, well, I hope I can do it at a very reasonable price.
I want to destroy my present self, my timid self.
Oh yeah! Let's go this far.
I want to destroy my current self, my cowardly self.
Wow yeah
Wow yeah, let's do it this way
I want to beat myself up for being so timid
Wow yeah
Okay, right?
Where do you think I am?
I don't know.
Is that all?
Yes.
Okay, thank you very much for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
This song...
When I first heard the song, my impression was that if the singer shifted the pitch of the modulation in the chorus even a millimeter, I could hear the chord. I thought it sounded like a very difficult song.
I call this kind of genre of music "thesaurus" or "thesaurus". Maybe it's just my way of saying it, but it has that kind of sad feeling, that kind of "class warfare" feeling, and I think the chorus is really like that.
I thought the chorus was very much like that, but if the singer doesn't sing it properly, it doesn't come across. It's like a zero or a hundred kind of song.
I felt like I was singing as if I was playing a game. But when I listened to Takeuchi-san's song and this recording, it became very clear to me,
I thought that Takeuchi-san's singing voice and the fact that he could tell that this song was good was the most important skill of his, so I thought it was really wonderful.
I thought that the way she sang the song immediately after being told to do so in this recording session was as expected of Akari Takeuchi,
The song has a really wide range of pitches from the lowest to the highest, so I think it must be very difficult,
But when I see Angulum performing it, I think it is the perfect song for the current Angulum,
I want to destroy it, or rather, I want to destroy it, and there is Angulum who can destroy it, so I think it is a wonderful song that really suits the current Angulum.
That's all for now, this is the vocal recording of Akari Takeuchi, who wants to destroy Angulum.
Enjoying it? Watch the rest of the show!
Morning Musume。 23's Sei Fukumura and Morning Musume。 23's Sakura Oda.
Here's the next one. Tsubaki Factory's "No Mistake, No Crying Vocal Recording
Here's a look at the vocal recording of Rina Yofu from Tsubaki Factory's latest single, "No Mistake, No Cry, No Nonsense.
Okay, the first A melody, right?
Ehh...
It's the part where she says she's getting mature.
I'm thinking of filming it half and half.
The bottom part you just sang.
And the top one.
She's getting older.
Okay, let's do it that way.
I'm trying to sing softly.
I'd rather sing backwards than forwards.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
Let's do it.
I've been told lately that I'm getting more mature.
I'm becoming more like you I was trying to be taller
Yeah, that's what it feels like.
I'll be me again.
A little more... it's still a little too bright right now.
Darker.
I'm getting more mature these days.
I've been mumbling a little bit lately.
Can you sing to yourself?
I'm sure that's what people are saying these days.
I'm becoming more like you because I've grown up so much
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Something like that.
Can you add more edge voice?
It suits me.
No, I like it. I'll put in what I can.
Let's try it, honey.
I'll give it a shot.
I've been told recently that I've grown mature.
I'll be the one that fits you, the one you've been trying to grow up to be.
OK, let's go to B melody.
Isn't it long?
We're up to four now.
I want to end it with "Ma-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da".I'd like to end up with a "maaaybe a different maaaybe a different maa
I don't want it to be the same.
Up, up, up...
I don't want to stop there.
The entrance.
It's so bright.
Blinding!
It's like... It's like... It's like...
I'm drinking... and then I'm...
It's like...
Why don't you just dash up there?
That's right, I'm losing track
Maa!
Keep the "maw" sound.
Mmm.
It's dazzling.
Yes.
The "maw" will grow longer.
It's too bright.
Maybe I should shorten it a little.
Okay.
Hold it up.
Let's just take a shot of him with his face up.
Okay.
I want to make it a little more intense.
Raise your face.
Raise it a little more.
Yes, sir.
There's a kind of love that gets stronger every time you do it.
Raise your face
Then, let's go to the chorus.
I who fell in love with you
Now it still hurts
I'm just plain embarrassed
It's not just that I lost you
The world has changed since I met you
No regrets, no love, no nothing. I'll hold on to the future
I met you
I met you, I met you, I met you
That's right, that's what I'm going to do.
The last three lines, get more rhythm.
Rhythm, the world, no regrets, no love, embrace the future
That's how conscious I want you to be
And, hey, let's do the "It still hurts right now, but...
It still hurts now, but...
That's right!
Do
Let's make it a little sad.
Yes, sir.
Look up.
I fell in love with you, and it still hurts.
But it's not just that I lost you.
The world has changed since I met you
No regrets, no love, no nothing.
Okay, next block, I'll just preempt two lines.
Already here, it's like a very wispy edge voice.
Seisupai no Tsuyogari, BAREKARAKUNAGAWARAWANIWA.
Seppai no Tsuyogari Reincarnated me de
I can't do anything.
No, that was good.
And, you know, if anything, you should cry a little more like this
Cry
Yes, I want to make it a little sad.
Yes, that's more important.
That's more important.
Yes.
Darker.
Is that what you're doing? It's always harder to sing here than at home.
If we darken it? Just a little. If you darken it too much, the picture won't show up.
Yes, it's easier to sing these songs when I'm closed up all the time.
You're so artistic.
Do you want me to dim the lights a little? I'll darken the eyes a little.
Can you do that? Is it? Yes, sir.
I've never seen anyone say that before, but it happens all the time.
When you sing, you should do it like this.
It's easier to sing when you're actually moving your body.
I'm a new me, born again.
Okay, it's okay. I'll take it with this.
I see. Darkening the eyes is new, isn't it?I see. Darkening the eyes is new, isn't it?
But I'm going to make my vision my world.
Then you get to that series, and wow! I'm like, "Wow!
No, it's interesting. I think it's good.
OK, done!
OK, good job!
I often feel like Reno is in full swing. Yes, it was. It was a lot of fun.
Not only was her voice great, but the recording was fun to the eyes as well.
I think the addition of Luno's voice to Tsubaki Factory's songs is a great change.
The unit is the same, but when I hear Luno's voice like this, it makes me feel like I'm a part of Tsubaki Factory.
I was impressed by the fact that a cool girl joined Tsubaki. I feel that he fits perfectly with Tsubaki. I'm amazed that Luno-chan is able to be so relaxed and not erase her own personality.
I could tell from the recording video that Luno-chan was able to be so relaxed without losing her own personality, so I thought it would be easier to sing here at home.
It's hard to have that kind of feeling with the director. I think about it a lot. I think everyone thinks about it, but they don't say it out loud. Yes, yes, but we can't say it out loud.
It's amazing that you can say such things and then hide your eyes to express them properly.
I think it's a wonderful thing about Yofuruno, and I hope she will continue to grow in this way.
That's all for now, this is Tsubaki Factory's "No Mistake, No Crying" vocal recording of Runo Yofuruno.
ANGELUM
Angelem's new album "Pick Club! NOW ON SALE
Let's take it easy today.
Mizuki Fukumura and Sakura Oda have been with us for the past few days, and now it's time to say goodbye.
We've watched various videos this time, and I, Sakura Oda, watched the recording video of Runo Yofu, who is now 15 years old, which is when she turns 6.
When we were that age, we didn't have any images like this, but now, I've seen the images of myself who thought I was good at singing in the past.
But now, when I look back at the images of myself who thought I was good at singing in the past, I am surprised to see that I couldn't sing at all, right?
I looked back at the video, and I thought I was 15 years old, so I was like, "I'm a crying adolescent boy," or "I'm 16 years old.
I thought, "I'd like to look back at the footage," and I thought, "I'm 15, so I'm a crying adolescent boy, or I'm 16, or 15 or 16, and there's probably no footage left from that period of recording, so I'd really like to see it.
I really love the system of preserving this recording footage of Upokami, and I want to look back on it, and I thought again that the other members of Hello!
I, Fukumura, was particularly impressed by Akari Takeuchi's vocal recording.
I want to destroy it.
I'll never forget the look on Shuri's face when she appeared on stage crying after hearing the cheers of the fans.
I'll never forget the look on your face when you came out crying after hearing the fans cheering for you.
I wondered how she was feeling as she was recording the song, and since I was about to graduate, I wondered how she was feeling as she was recording the song.
I was also able to think about how I would feel when I record a song since I'm about to graduate.
In up-cam, we'll be going behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Up-Front Group. We'll be showing you things you don't normally see, so please subscribe to our channel!
This time, UpCami will be talking with Sei FUKUMURA of Morning Musume。 23 and Sakura Oda of Morning Musume。 23's Sakura Oda.
Good bye!
Next time on Upokami,
Beyonce's recording of "Seek Me, Destiny's Traveler",
And we will show you how Juice-Juice arranged the hair of one of the members.
Please look forward to it!
Please subscribe to our channel!